[
    {
      "question": "What does PHP stand for?",
      "option": [
        "Private Home Page",
        "PHP: Hypertext Preprocessor",
        "Personal Hypertext Processor"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "PHP server scripts are surrounded by delimiters, which?",
      "option": [
        "<script>...</script>",
        "<?php...?>",
        "<?php>...</?>",
        "<&>...</&>"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you write \"Hello World\" in PHP",
      "option": [
        "Document.Write(\"Hello World\");",
        "\"Hello World\";",
        "echo \"Hello World\";"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "All variables in PHP start with which symbol?",
      "option": [
        "!",
        "&",
        "$"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct way to end a PHP statement?",
      "option": [
        ".",
        "New line",
        "</php>",
        ";"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "The PHP syntax is most similar to:",
      "option": [
        "JavaScript",
        "Perl and C",
        "VBScript"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you get information from a form that is submitted using the \"get\" method?",
      "option": [
        "$_GET[];",
        "Request.QueryString;",
        "Request.Form;"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "When using the POST method, variables are displayed in the URL:",
      "option": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "In PHP you can use both single quotes ( ' ' ) and double quotes ( \" \" ) for strings:",
      "option": [
        "False",
        "True"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "Include files must have the file extension \".inc\"",
      "option": [
        "False",
        "True"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct way to include the file \"time.inc\" ?",
      "option": [
        "<?php include:\"time.inc\"; ?>",
        "<?php include \"time.inc\"; ?>",
        "<?php include file=\"time.inc\"; ?>",
        "<!-- include file=\"time.inc\" -->"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct way to create a function in PHP?",
      "option": [
        "new_function myFunction()",
        "function myFunction()",
        "create myFunction()"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct way to open the file \"time.txt\" as readable?",
      "option": [
        "open(\"time.txt\");",
        "fopen(\"time.txt\",\"r\");",
        "open(\"time.txt\",\"read\");",
        "fopen(\"time.txt\",\"r+\");"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "PHP allows you to send emails directly from a script",
      "option": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which superglobal variable holds information about headers, paths, and script locations?",
      "option": [
        "$GLOBALS",
        "$_SERVER",
        "$_GET",
        "$_SESSION"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "What is the correct way to add 1 to the $count variable?",
      "option": [
        "count++;",
        "++count",
        "$count++;",
        "$count =+1"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "What is a correct way to add a comment in PHP?",
      "option": [
        "<comment>...</comment>",
        "<!--...-->",
        "*\\...\\*",
        "/*...*/"
      ],
      "correct": 3
    },
    {
      "question": "PHP can be run on Microsoft Windows IIS(Internet Information Server):",
      "option": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "The die() and exit() functions do the exact same thing.",
      "option": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which one of these variables has an illegal name?",
      "option": [
        "$my-Var",
        "$my_Var",
        "$myVar"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you create a cookie in PHP?",
      "option": [
        "makecookie()",
        "setcookie()",
        "createcookie"
      ],
      "correct": 1
    },
    {
      "question": "In PHP, the only way to output text is with echo.",
      "option": [
        "False",
        "True"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "How do you create an array in PHP?",
      "option": [
        "$cars = array[\"Volvo\", \"BMW\", \"Toyota\"];",
        "$cars = \"Volvo\", \"BMW\", \"Toyota\";",
        "$cars = array(\"Volvo\", \"BMW\", \"Toyota\");"
      ],
      "correct": 2
    },
    {
      "question": "The if statement is used to execute some code only if a specified condition is true",
      "option": [
        "True",
        "False"
      ],
      "correct": 0
    },
    {
      "question": "Which operator is used to check if two values are equal and of same data type?",
      "option": [
        "===",
        "!=",
        "=",
        "=="
      ],
      "correct": 0
    }
  ]